## **BHOOMI BHAMANI**

Add: A-501, Kaveri Soham,

B/H Divyajyot School,

Shilaj, Ahmedabad - 380059, Gujarat – India.

Contact: +91-9724730645

Mail: bhoomibhamani@gmail.com

Certified Professional in Human Resource Field: I have total 3+ year of experience in human resource in different field. Apart from that specialization to develop new corporate including to build new admin and HR department including all bottom to top activities.

Professional Skills			
	Effective Communication		Employee's recruitment in effective manner
	HR Department startup		Induction, Orientation & training for new employee
	Effective Admin Startup		Employee's documentation and personal file making
	Build HR policies rules and regulations		Employee's Joining & Exit formalities
	HR Documentation		Performance appraisal and monthly appraisal
	Vendor and account management		Celebrate festivals, birthdays and work anniversaries
	Office expenses management		Attendance & Payroll management
	Problem solving		And other admin & HR related work

## **Professional Experience:**

 SOFARSOLAR India Pvt. Ltd. (Shenzhen SOFARSOLAR Ltd company- China) (Ass. Manager in HR & Admin) April 2019 to Oct. 2020

SOFARSOLAR (est. 2012) is one of the subsidiaries of SOFAR Group in China and specializes in R&D, production, sales and service of grid-tied inverters ranging from 1kW to 7.5kW (residential), 10kW to 70kW (commercial) and other related renewable products. SOFARSOLAR with more than 400 employees, has a very strong and experienced R&D team who have improved inverter technology both software and hardware. SOFARSOLAR inverters have been installed in 40+ countries (e.g. Australia, the UK, Italy, Belgium, Spain, Netherland, France, China etc.) with currently 4 own subsidiaries in Australia, Wuxi, Beijing, Shenzhen and Henan.

- Threeway Group, Ahmedabad. (HR & Admin Head & Working partner) Jan 2019 to March 2019
   Threeway Group is providing multiple services like office setup for computer laptop and networking,
   Digital Marketing, Student's projects & training Etc.
- Dash Technologies Inc., Ahmedabad (HR & Admin Executive): April 2018 to Dec 2018 Dash
  Technologies is USA based IT & Recruitment Company. Where they are doing offshore recruitment
  for IT companies in USA and also into product & service base IT services like web application, mobile
  application web development, product development etc.
- Raijin Solar Energy, Ahmedabad (HR Executive):Dec 2016 to Feb 2018

  Raijin Solar Energy Is a leading Photo voltaic(PV) Installer, EPC Contractor, Importer and Supplier of all kind of solar products. They are working with good companies as a subcontractor for PV Installer.
- Rajasthan Chhatarbhuj Hospitals (GRMI), Ahmedabad (HR Clerk): Oct 2013 to Feb 2014 The Gujarat Research & Medical Institute (Rajasthan Hospitals) is a charitable trust, founded and registered in the year 1982, when the members felt dearth of specialty health care facilities in and around the city of Ahmedabad and more so in Gujarat, Rajasthan and Madhya Pradesh

## **Education Qualification:**

- **S.S.C.** from Gujarat board in year 2007 with **76.23**% from H.B. Kapadia New High School, Shahibaug, Ahmedabad.
- H.S.C. from Gujarat board in year 2009 with 66% from H.B. Kapadia New High School, Shahibaug, Ahmedabad.
- B.Com from Gujarat University in year 2012 with Pass class from G.L.S. IC, Law Garden, Ahmedabad.
- Post-Graduation Diploma in Human Resources Management in year 2013 with B grade from G.L.S.
   Institute for Management Excellence.

## **Personal Details:**

Full Name: Bhoomi Manishhbhai Bhamani

Date Of Birth: 8<sup>th</sup> December, 1991

• Nationality: Indian

Hobbies: Travelling, Gossiping with friends, Socialism, Web surfing etc.

Open to Relocate Globally.